{
    "subject": "resource/Scoop_(2006_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Ian_McShane",
    "human_readable": "Ian McShane stars in the film Scoop.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9684029817581177,
            "question": "What role does Ian McShane play in Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8460131883621216,
            "question": "In what movie does Ian McShane appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8435470461845398,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Ian McShane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8181872367858887,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8005513548851013,
            "question": "Is Ian McShane an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7017603516578674,
            "question": "Can you name another film starring Ian McShane?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5931169390678406,
            "question": "Who directed the film Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40045544505119324,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3308943510055542,
            "question": "Is Scoop a recent film release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27598533034324646,
            "question": "What genre is the film Scoop likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ian McShane stars in the film Scoop.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8272_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Scoop a recent film release?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8272_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of the film Scoop?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8272_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film Scoop?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8272_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8272_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this response is that multiple documents mention Ian McShane being associated with the film \"Scoop\". Specifically, one document states \" \u201cScoop\u201d stars Hugh Jackman, Scarlett Johansson, Ian McShane and Woody Allen.\" while another document refers to Ian McShane as Joe Strombel in the same movie."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Ian McShane stars in the film \"Scoop,\" which directly supports the statement that Ian McShane stars in the film Scoop."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}